OH.
HELLO.
THAT WAS QUICK.
HMM.
WELL, OBVIOUSLY I KNOW THE HOUSE, SO...
SO YOU HAVE AN UNFAIR ADVANTAGE.
UNFAIR ADVANTAGE. YES.
MMM.
WELL, LET'S...
COME ON IN.
ARE YOU NOT GOING TO GET THE...?
OH.
SORRY, WE WEREN'T PROPERLY INTRODUCED.
I'M IAN, BY THE WAY.
HELLO.
HOLD ON, JUST...
OH.
IT'S RACHEL, ISN'T IT?
REBECCA.
I WORK WITH JEREMY.
OH.
I SAY WORK WITH.
I'M MORE ON THE IT SIDE.
BUT OBVIOUSLY WITH HIM
BEING THE OFFICE MANAGER,
THERE IS A FAIR AMOUNT OF OVERLAP.
HE'S MORE RESPONSIBLE FOR INFRASTRUCTURE
WHEREAS I TAKE MORE OF A LEAD
IN PROGRAM DEVELOP...
RIGHT.
WHAT DID YOU SAY YOUR NAME WAS AGAIN?
IT'S IAN.
THAT'S RIGHT, YES,
JEREMY HAS MENTIONED YOU.
MMM.
SHH.
WONDER WHO THAT WAS?
DON'T KNOW.
IT COULD BE A LONG GAME.
YES.
SO, HOW DOES IT FEEL
TO BE ENGAGED, RACHEL?
REBECCA.
HAVE YOU SET A DATE YET?
THE 9TH OF NOVEMBER.
OH, DEAR.
THAT'S 9/11.
YOU'LL NOT FORGET THAT IN A HURRY,
WILL YOU?
OH.
NO, I HADN'T THOUGHT OF IT THAT WAY,
TO BE HONEST.
WELL, YOU MUST.
UM, I WAS CHRISTENED
RICHARD IAN PERCIVAL,
IF YOU CAN BELIEVE THAT.
RIP.
BOO.
OH, CARL. GET IN QUICK.
I HEARD YOU TALKING.
VERY SLACK, REBECCA.
WHY ARE YOU HIDING IN HERE?
I DIDN'T CHOOSE IT, DID I?
GUILTY AS CHARGED.
HAVE YOU MET IAN?
NO, I DON'T BELIEVE
I'VE HAD THE PLEASURE.
CARL. I'M REBECCA'S BROTHER.
SO YOU MUST KNOW ALL THE NOOKS
AND CRANNIES OF THE HOUSE THEN?
OH, YES.
I SPENT MOST OF MY CHRISTMASES
HIDING IN VARIOUS CUPBOARDS
WAITING FOR MY BOSSY
LITTLE SISTER TO FIND ME.
YOU NEVER COULD THOUGH, COULD YOU?
GET IN.
IS DADDY PLAYING?
HE SAID HE WOULD.
HE'S OUT SHOWING MARK
AND ELIZABETH THE STABLES.
WELL, HE CAN DO THAT AFTERWARDS!
WE'RE MEANT TO BE PLAYING THE GAME!
IT'S ALL RIGHT, KEEP YOUR VOICE DOWN.
YOU'LL GIVE US ALL AWAY.
YEAH, CHILL OUT, BITCH.
SORRY, THAT WAS MISJUDGED.
ACTUALLY, IT WAS QUITE FUNNY.
SHE IS A BIT OF A BITCH,
AREN'T YOU, BECKS?
LOLLIPOPS.
COME AND GET YOUR LOLLIPOPS.
WHERE ARE THOSE CHILDREN HIDING?
NOW THEN, IF I WERE GOING
TO SECRETE MESELF IN THIS ROOM,
WHERE WOULD I GO?
NOT BEHIND THOSE CURTAINS,
THEY'RE A MIGRAINE WAITING TO HAPPEN.
OH, HANGING AROUND THE TOILETS, PERHAPS.
IT HAS BEEN KNOWN.
OR WOULD I ENJOY
SPENDING TIME IN THE CLOSET?
OH! NOT INTERRUPTING ANYTHING, I HOPE?
COME ON.
WHOA, IT'S LIKE THE BACK ROOM
OF CINDERELLA'S AT WAKEFIELD.
HAS ANYONE GOT ANY POPPERS OR LUBE?
STUART.
YOU TWO KNOW EACH OTHER THEN, DO YOU?
UNFORTUNATELY, YES.
THEY' RE PARTNERS.
IN WHAT LINE?
UH, WELL, IT USED TO BE STRAIGHT UP
AND DOWN, BUT NOT ANYMORE.
I'M IN IT.
CONGRATULATIONS. I'M IN SHIT,
COS I GOT IN LATE LAST NIGHT, DIDN'T I?
STUART, YOU CAN DO WHAT YOU LIKE,
IT DOESN'T BOTHER ME.
OH, I SEE.
YOU'RE "LIVING TOGETHER" PARTNERS?
OH, YEAH, WE'RE QUEER, DEAR.
GET USED TO IT.
ALL RIGHT, THAT'S IT,
I CAN'T STAY HERE...
CARL, PLEASE.
STUART, BEHAVE.
THIS PARTY IS NOT ABOUT YOU.
IT'S ABOUT ME AND JEREMY, SO BUTT OUT!
CARL.
YOU'RE MUCH PRETTIER
WHEN YOU'RE ANGRY AND SO ARE YOU.
ANYWAY, CHANGING THE SUBJECT SLIGHTLY,
I'M NOT BEING FUNNY,
BUT THERE'S A MAN DOWNSTAIRS
THAT ABSOLUTELY STINKS.
YES, THAT'S STINKY JOHN.
AND WHAT IS IT?
IS IT HIS CLOTHES, HIS BREATH?
I DON'T KNOW.
HE WAS AT SCHOOL WITH US,
WASN'T HE, CARL?
YES, THAT'S WHEN HE WAS JUST JOHN,
NOT STINKY JOHN.
SOMETHING MUST HAVE HAPPENED TO HIM.
HE JUST STOPPED WASHING ONE DAY.
MAYBE WE SHOULD TRACE IT BACK.
MAYBE WE SHOULD.
WHO DO YOU STINK YOU ARE?
AND WHAT ABOUT ALL THE OTHER ONES,
WHO'S THAT BORING ONE?
YES, AND ERM...
WHAT ABOUT THAT OLD WOMAN
THAT'S WANDERING AROUND?
OH, GOD, THAT'S GERALDINE.
SHE'S DADDY'S CLEANER.
I ASKED HER TO COME AND SERVE DRINKS
BUT SHE THINKS SHE'S A GUEST.
THAT IS HILAR.
YOU'VE GOT TO TELL HER.
I CAN'T NOW. SHE'S ALL DRESSED UP.
DRESSED UP?
SHE LOOKS LIKE FEED THE BIRDS.
THERE'S A SANDWICH MAN
AT WORK WHO, ERM,
WEARS A YELLOW T-SHIRT, THIS...
A JERSEY, BUT IT'S T-SHIRT MATERIAL.
AND ALL THE GIRLS CALL HIM
MUSTARD MIKE.
WELL, THANK GOD
I BROUGHT CHAMPAGNE.
WHO WANTS A SWIG?
FOUND THEM! THEY'RE HERE!
SHH.
THAT'S IT, ISN'T IT? I'VE WON?
NO, YOU'VE GOT TO HIDE AS WELL.
OH, OKAY.
NO, IN HERE WITH US.
OH, THERE'S NOT
REALLY MUCH SPACE IN THERE.
THAT'S WHY IT'S FUN, APPARENTLY.
I'M A LITTLE BIT CLAUSTROPHOBIC.
THEN IT'S EVEN MORE FUN.
QUICK, BEFORE SOMEONE SEES YOU.
SO, WHAT HAPPENS NOW?
WE WAIT FOR THE OTHERS TO FIND US.
SO HOW DO YOU WIN?
NOBODY WINS. YOU JUST WAIT.
OH.
RIGHT.
SO WHEN DOES THE GAME START?
THIS IS THE GAME, RACHEL.
WE'RE PLAYING IT.
OH.
SO YOU'RE RACHEL, ARE YOU?
YES, HELLO.
BECAUSE I'VE BEEN CALLING
REBECCA RACHEL, HAVEN'T I?
YES.
I THINK I JUST GOT MIXED UP BECAUSE
JEREMY TALKS ABOUT YOU ALL THE TIME.
DOES HE?
YES.
WHO ARE YOU TALKING TO?
WHICH ONE ARE YOU AGAIN?
REBECCA.
YES.
OH, I'VE NOT SEEN THIS MUCH
WOOD SINCE I WAS...
DON'T.
SO WHAT DOES JEREMY SAY ABOUT ME?
I'M SORRY.
AT WORK, YOU SAID HE TALKS ABOUT ME.
OH, JUST...
THE USUAL BORING GIRLFRIEND STUFF.
BORING GIRLFRIEND?
NOT THAT YOU'RE BORING,
JUST THE STUFF HE SAYS ABOUT YOU IS...
BORING?
YES.
WELL, COMING FROM YOU, IAN,
THAT'S QUITE SOMETHING. THANK YOU.
YOU'RE WELCOME.
IS ANYONE ELSE GETTING HOT?
I JUST NEED TO OPEN THE DOOR A CRACK.
I JUST NEED TO GET SOME AIR.
WAIT TILL STINKY JOHN GETS HERE,
YOU'LL NEED MORE THAN A CRACK.
IS STINKY JOHN PLAYING?
EVERYBODY'S PLAYING. IT'S SARDINES.
OH, I DON'T KNOW IF
I CAN STAY IN HERE IF HE GETS IN.
I DO GET A LITTLE BIT, ERM...
DON'T WORRY, DEAR, ME AND YOU
WILL NIP THROUGH TO NARNIA,
HAVE A SNOWBALL FIGHT,
GET SOME TURKISH DELIGHT.
OH, SORRY, I NEED TO BREATHE.
NO, YOU'RE NOT ALLOWED...
SHE'S ALLOWED TO BREATHE.
I WOULDN'T MIND STRETCHING
THE OLD LEGS ACTUALLY.
BEEN IN HERE A WHILE.
WHAT? OH, THIS IS RIDICULOUS.
I'M GOING TO HAVE A PEE BREAK THEN,
THAT CHAMPAGNE'S GONE RIGHT THROUGH ME.
WELL, DON'T FLUSH IT.
OH, DON'T WORRY, I WON'T.
YOU KNOW MY MOTTO.
IF IT'S YELLOW, LET IT MELLOW,
IF IT'S BROWN, FLUSH IT DOWN.
OH! OCCUPIED.
SORRY!
WELL, THAT'S SOMETHING
I SHALL NEVER UN-SEE.
WHO IS IT?
FEED THE BIRDS.
GERALDINE.
SHOULDN'T SHE BE USING
THE STAFF TOILETS?
YOU OKAY?
WHAT'S THE MATTER WITH YOU?
WELL, WHAT DO YOU THINK, REBECCA?
LOOK WHERE WE ARE.
OH, THERE YOU GO, LOVEY. DOESN'T
HAVE A LOCK, IT'S AN EN SUITEY.
YOU'VE WARMED THE SEAT FOR ME.
I HEARD YOU ALL TALKING IN THERE,
I JUST DIDN'T WANT TO DISTURB YOU.
THAT'S A BONNY DRESS.
THANK YOU. I GOT IT IN PARIS.
MY HIP WENT THAT COLOR WHEN I FELL
UP SOME STEPS AT LEGOLAND.
I WAS JUST GETTING SOME AIR.
I'M A BIT CLAUSTROPHOBIC.
IS THAT WHERE YOU CAN'T BEAR
TOUCH A SNAKE?
YOU'VE GOT THAT, HAVEN'T YOU, CARL?
I'D HARDLY CALL IT
A SNAKE, STUART.
MORE LIKE A SCALY LIZARD.
I HEARD THAT.
GOOD.
RIGHT. SHALL WE, UH,
ASSUME THE POSITION?
IT'S JUST A GAME.
JUST BE A SEC.
WAIT FOR ME.
ROOM FOR A LITTLE 'UN?
OF COURSE THERE IS.
IT'S LIKE THE TIME AND RELATIVE
DIMENSION IN SPACE.
TARDIS.
SO, RACHEL, TELL ME AGAIN
HOW YOU KNOW JEREMY'?
ERM...
RACHEL IS JEREMY'S EX, GERALDINE.
OH, THAT'S IT.
I KNEW IT WAS SOMETHING
I WASN'T SUPPOSED TO MENTION.
WE'RE JUST MATES NOW.
WE'RE TEXT BUDDIES.
HE BBM'S ME EVERY NOW AND AGAIN
AT WEEKENDS.
OH, LOVELY.
YEAH, HE BBM'S ME A LOT TOO.
ALWAYS, ER, BBM-ING.
WHAT IT IS TO BE YOUNG.
IT'S BEEN AGES SINCE
I'VE BEEN IN THIS ROOM.
YOUR DAD USUALLY KEEPS IT LOCKED.
YOU KNOW, AFTER...
WE'RE NOT GOING
DOWN THAT ROAD, GERALDINE.
IT'S A... IT'S A PARTY, REMEMBER?
OH, YES.
♪ WHY AM I ALWAYS THE BRIDESMAID
♪ NEVER THE BLUSHING BRIDE
♪ DING DONG WEDDING BELLS
♪ ONLY RING FOR OTHER GIRLS
♪ ONE FINE DAY
♪ OH, LET IT BE SOON
I SHALL WAKE UP
♪ IN THE MORNING
ON MY OWN HONEYMOON ♪
RIGHT, I'M COMING BACK IN. NOBODY FART.
SMELL THAT. CARBOLIC.
WE SHOULD GET SOME OF THAT
FOR OUR EN SUITEY.
THIS IS FUN, ISN'T IT?
THANK YOU, GERALDINE.
YES, IT IS FUN.
DO YOU HAVE A GIRLFRIEND, IAN?
OH, NO. NO.
YOUNG, FREE AND SINGLE, AT THE MOMENT.
I'VE NOT BEEN A MONK.
I'VE HAD SOME EXPERIENCES, BUT NO.
PRETTY BARREN AT THE MOMENT.
A PRETTY ARID PATCH.
OH.
WE HAVE TO GET HIM FIXED UP, WON'T WE?
YES.
DO YOU LIKE HIM, RACHEL?
NO, NO, NO.
I'M SORRY.
I HAVE A BOYFRIEND
WHOSE NAME'S LEE.
DID YOU MEET HIM DOWNSTAIRS?
YES.
HE GAVE ME HIS JACKET AND ASKED ME
TO GET HIM A DRINK.
OH, HE'S ONLY YOUNG.
HOW YOUNG? IS HE LEGAL?
HE'S 21.
OH, A TOY BOY.
YOU KNOW WHAT THEY SAY, IF THERE'S GRASS
ON THE WICKET, LET PLAY COMMENCE.
OH, FOR FUCK'S SAKE, STUART,
GIVE IT A REST.
WHAT'S GOT INTO YOU?
CAN'T YOU JUST TALK LIKE A NORMAL
HUMAN BEING FOR FIVE MINUTES?
SHH.
MARK, IN HERE.
HAVE YOU MANAGED TO GET RID OF HIM YET?
YEAH, HE'S GONE OFF
TO LOOK FOR THE OTHERS.
GOD, I LOATHE PLAYING OTHER PEOPLE'S
FAMILY GAMES. IT IS SUCH A BORE.
WE SHOULD HAVE BEEN DONE BY NOW.
YOU SAID WE'D BE AWAY BY THREE.
WELL, WHY DON'T YOU JUST DO
THE LIE ABOUT THE BABYSITTER BEING ILL?
BECAUSE IT NEEDS TO BE SEEDED.
YOU NEED TO SEED IT.
IT DOESN'T NEED TO BE SEEDED,
YOU JUST SAY IT.
"OH, I'M AWFULLY SORRY,
WE'VE GOT TO GO NOW.
"BABYSITTER IS NOT
FELLING VERY WELL." BOOM.
YOU'RE SO NAIVE, MARK.
LISTEN, LISTEN,
OLD MAN MAYBE TEDIOUS, BUT
HE'S OUR WAY INTO DICKY LAWRENCE, YEAH?
SO WE HAVE TO PUT A SHIFT IN.
I THOUGHT YOU HATED DICKY LAWRENCE.
YEAH, I HATE DICKY LAWRENCE,
HE'S A FIRST-CLASS PRICK.
BUT I NEED HIM TO SMOOTH
OVER THAT MERGER NEXT YEAR, YOU KNOW.
YOU KNOW WHAT THEY SAY,
KEEP YOUR FRIENDS CLOSE...
BUT YOUR ENEMIES CLOSER.
OH, YOU'RE SUCH A HORRIBLE SHIT, MARK.
THAT'S WHY YOU BLOODY LOVE ME.
MARK, STOP IT.
COME ON.
JUST FINGERS.
SOMEONE COULD WALK IN ON THEM.
YEAH, WELL THAT'S
THE THRILL OF IT, GERALDINE.
GET OUT THE WAY, I'M GOING TO FILM IT.
NO, YOU DON'T, PERVERT.
QUICK, SOMEONE MAKE A NOISE.
I THINK THAT WAS A BIT TOO SUBTLE, IAN.
GERONIMO!
FUCK!
OH, YOU FOUND US.
WELL DONE.
WHAT THE HELL?
SARDINES.
HELLO, MARK.
WELCOME TO THE WARDROBE.
IAN. I WORK FOR YOU...
IN IT.
OF COURSE, HI. YEAH.
WE'VE BEEN HIDING IN HERE FOR AGES
WAITING FOR SOMEONE TO FIND US
AND THESE DOORS ARE SO THICK.
WE DIDN'T HEAR ANYTHING, DID WE?
NO, NO.
DO YOU WANT TO COME IN THEN,
BEFORE DADDY FINDS US?
ERM...
YEAH, I'M A TEENY BIT
WORRIED ABOUT THE BABYSITTER.
SHE SAID SHE'S FEELING
UNDER THE WEATHER.
OH, WELL SEEDED.
NO, I'M SURE WE'LL BE ALL RIGHT
FOR A FEW MINUTES, WON'T WE? YEAH.
YEAH, LOOKS LIKE A LOT OF FUN.
MMM-HMM, MMM-HMM, MMM-HMM.
ALL RIGHT,
I'M GETTING IN.
YES. EVERYBODY WATCH MY SHOES.
OR MAYBE I SHOULD JUST TAKE THEM OFF.
JUST GET IN, LIZ.
IT'S GOOD, THE SOONER WE START.
YOU STAND THERE NEXT TO RACHEL.
REBECCA.
SORRY.
IT'S MY ENGAGEMENT PARTY
AND NOBODY SEEMS TO KNOW MY NAME.
NO, IT'S JUST THAT, UH,
YOU KNOW, JEREMY ALWAYS SAYS...
WHAT?
ERM, THIS ONE'S RACHEL.
OH, HELLO.
NICE TO MEET YOU.
NICE TO MEET YOU, TOO.
AH.
THERE YOU ARE.
I'VE ALREADY BEEN IN HERE ONCE.
LEE, COME IN, WE'RE HAVING SUCH A LAUGH.
WARDROBE. CAN'T BELIEVE I DIDN'T
CHECK THE FUCKING WARDROBE. KNOB.
ALL RIGHT? I THOUGHT I HEARD
SOMEONE SHOUTING.
YEAH, THAT WAS ME.
I SAID, "GERONIMO."
DON'T ASK ME WHY.
HAVE YOU MET EVERYONE, LEE?
THIS IS IAN, HE WORKS WITH MARK.
FOR MARK, ACTUALLY. I OWN THE COMPANY.
OH, YEAH.
WELL, IF YOU EVER NEED
ANY ROOFING DOING.
YOU KNOW REBECCA, OBVIOUSLY.
AND THIS IS MARK'S WIFE, ELIZABETH.
HELLO.
HI.
YOU ALL RIGHT?
YOU LIKE YOU'VE BEEN CRYING.
OH, IT'S JUST A LITTLE BIT DUSTY
IN HERE, THAT'S ALL.
AND, UH, THIS IS REBECCA'S BROTHER CARL.
AND THAT'S STU, HIS...
FLATMATE. PLEASED TO MEET YOU.
FLATMATE?
RIG HT.
AND THIS IS GERALDINE.
OH, YEAH, I KNOW, YEAH.
WOULDN'T MIND A CHEEKY TOP UP,
IF YOU DON'T MIND, LOVE.
PARDON?
A LITTLE CHEEKY CHAMPERS,
THERE'S A GOOD GIRL.
WHY DO YOU KEEP ASKING ME?
WELL, REBECCA SAID
YOU WERE SERVING DRINKS.
NO. NO.
NO, I'M A GUEST.
HE'S GOT HIS WIRES CROSSED.
YES, WE'RE ALL GUESTS HERE. ALL EQUAL.
I USED TO BE THEIR NANNY.
I'VE KNOWN ALL THREE OF THEM
SINCE THEY WERE SO HIGH.
THREE OF THEM?
MM.
YES, WE HAVE A SISTER, CAROLINE.
IS SHE NOT COMING, BECKY?
LOVE TO SEE THE BOYS AGAIN.
THEY MUST BE GETTING QUITE BIG NOW.
AHEM, NO, THEY CAN'T MAKE IT.
IT'S A BIT TOO FAR TO TRAVEL.
OH.
I'LL GO AND GET ME OWN DRINK THEN,
SHALL I?
HERE WE GO, LEE.
I'VE GOT SOME CONTRABAND YOU CAN HAVE.
WE'LL FORM A SPLINTER GROUP
UNDER THE BED.
YOU CAN'T DO THAT.
OH, IT'S ALL RIGHT.
I'M SURE MY FLATMATE WON'T MIND.
COME ON THEN.
MMM.
DON'T YOU TRY AND BURN ME.
I'M SORRY, STUART,
BUT THAT'S AGAINST THE RULES.
ER, HOMOPHOBIC.
OH, YOU'VE GOT THAT, HAVEN'T YOU, LOVEY?
NO, I'M CLAUSTROPHOBIC.
YEAH, WELL, IT IS
A LITTLE CROWDED IN HERE.
YES, IT'S ALMOST LIKE
WE'RE A TIN OF SARDINES.
ACTUALLY, COLIN, WHY DON'T YOU
STEP OUT FOR A MINUTE, YEAH?
GIVE US A BIT OF ROOM.
YES.
I MEAN, IT'S IAN. BUT, YES.
IAN. SORRY. IAN.
UNDER THE BED WITH THOSE TWO, YEAH.
SORRY. PRIVATE PARTY.
LOOK, YOU CANNOT PLAY
SARDINES UNLESS EVERYONE
IS HIDING IN THE SAME PLACE TOGETHER.
THAT'S WHAT MAKES IT FUN!
OH, YES. OH, LEE, THAT'S NICE.
OH, KEEP DOING THAT.
WHAT BIG HANDS YOU'VE GOT. OH, YES!
LEE?
BABE, I'M NOT DOING ANYTHING.
LEAVE HIM ALONE, STUART.
OH, WHAT'S THE MATTER, CARL?
ARE YOU JEALOUS?
PISS OFF.
STOP ARGUING, YOU TWO.
THIS IS RIDICULOUS.
IT'S NOT MY FAULT
YOU'RE AFRAID OF INTIMACY, CARL.
AND IT'S NOT FAULT EITHER.
YOU HAVE NO IDEA.
TA-DA.
JOHN.
OH,
LOOKS LIKE I'M ONE OF
THE LAST TO JOIN THE PARTY.
CAN I SQUEEZE IN?
NO.
I JUST THINK IT'S A BIT TOO FULL.
NO. THERE'S PLENTY OF ROOM.
I FEEL SICK.
BREATHE THROUGH YOUR MOUTH.
ACTUALLY, JOHN, SOME PEOPLE
ARE HIDING UNDER THE BED.
OH, NO, YOU DON'T.
COULD YOU SWAP?
I'M A BIT CLAUSTROPHOBIC.
THAT'S NOT THE GAME, IS IT?
YOU'RE ALL MEANT TO BE
SQUASHED IN TOGETHER.
THAT'S THE RULES.
YES, BUT WE THOUGHT IT DOESN'T REALLY
MATTER ABOUT THE RULES.
AS LONG AS WE'RE ALL IN
THE SAME ROOM, IT STILL COUNTS.
OH.
ALL RIGHT, AS YOU WISH.
ACTUALLY, JOHN, THERE REALLY ISN'T ROOM
UNDER HERE. THERE'S, ERM...
THERE'S SUITCASES AND EVERYTHING,
ISN'T THAT RIGHT, LEE?
YEAH, RIGHT, MATE.
SORRY.
OH .
OH, I DON'T THINK I'D FIT UNDER
THERE ANYWAY, TO BE HONEST.
WHAT WITH THE OLD 26 PACK.
YEAH, YOU'RE BETTER OFF
GOING WITH THE WARDROBE GROUP.
ALL RIGHT.
I'M BACK AGAIN.
HANG ON.
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
IS IT CAUGHT OR SOMETHING?
OH, IT'S STUCK, JOHN.
MAYBE TRY GOING IN THE BATHROOM.
FIRST TIME FOR EVERYTHING.
I CAN SEE WHAT IT IS.
IT'S FINGERS.
SOMEONE'S HOLDING IT WITH
THEIR FINGERS.
NO, WE'RE TRYING TO PUSH IT.
OH, LET HIM IN. POOR LAMB.
WE CAN'T. MARK, TELL THEM.
TRY GOING BEHIND THE CURTAIN.
OH.
ALL RIGHT.
FUNNIEST GAME OF SARDINES
I'VE EVER PLAYED.
AH.
YOU HAVEN'T SEEN REBECCA ANYWHERE,
HAVE YOU, JOHN?
CAUGHT RED-HANDED.
SHE'S, UH, HIDING IN THE WARDROBE.
BUT YOU CAN'T GET IN.
DOOR'S STUCK APPARENTLY.
RIGHT. THANKS.
AND THERE'S TWO UNDER THE BED.
IT'S A SHAMBLES.
BECKS,
IT'S JEREMY.
HI.
LISTEN, DARLING, I'VE JUST GOT
TO POP DOWN TO THE STATION
AND PICK UP A CHUM
WHO'S RUNNING A BIT LATE.
I CAN'T SEEM TO FIND MY KEYS.
YOU HAVEN'T HAD THEM, HAVE YOU?
UH, NO, THEY'RE IN YOUR JACKET.
NO, I'VE LOOKED,
THEY'RE NOT THERE.
IF I CAN'T FIND THEM, I MIGHT HAVE
TO TAKE THE MINI, IS THAT OKAY?
ALL RIGHT.
DRIVE SAFELY THOUGH.
I LOVE YOU.
I LOVE YOU TOO, RACHEL.
REBECCA.
ERM... REBECCA, I LOVE YOU.
WHAT IS THAT AWFUL SMELL?
HELLO, ANDREW.
SEARCHED THIS ROOM, HAVE YOU?
YES, I BELIEVE THERE ARE SOME
PEOPLE HIDING IN THE WARDROBE.
SOME UNDER THE BED AND STINKY JO...
AND JOHN IS BEHIND THE CURTAINS.
NO, THAT IS ABSOLUTELY WRONG.
COME OUT FROM THERE, BOY.
YOU ALL HAVE TO BE IN THE SAME PLACE.
THIS ISN'T HIDE AND GO SEEK.
YOU KNOW THE RULES, DON'T YOU?
WELL?
YES, SIR.
COME ON. OUT. OUT.
IT'S LIKE THE DIARY OF ANNE FRANK.
HI, DADDY.
FIVE MORE SARDINES TO GO IN THE TIN.
SORRY, ANDREW, IT'S JUST I NEED TO...
COME ON, IN YOU GO.
THAT'S IT.
UGH! SORRY, EVERYBODY.
THERE WE GO.
THAT'S THE NAME OF THE GAME, SARDINES.
THIS IS FUCKING MENTAL.
OH, I'VE GOT...
I'VE GOT TO TWEET A PICTURE OF THIS.
OH, GOD, HERE YOU ARE.
ALL RIGHT, SMILE, EVERYONE.
IT'S JUST THEY
BOTH START WITH AN R, SO, I ER...
WOULD ANYONE LIKE A MINT?
JOHN?
NO, THANK YOU.
ARE YOU SURE? THEY'RE VERY REFRESHING.
THEY, ER, GIVE ME DIARRHEA.
OH, DEAR GOD.
I'LL HAVE ONE ACTUALLY. I'VE GOT
SOMETHING CATCHING IN ME THROAT.
PASS 'EM AROUND.
HERE.
ANDREW, ELIZABETH WAS JUST
ASKING AFTER DICKY LAWRENCE.
HOW IS HE THESE DAYS?
DICKY LAWRENCE?
I HAVEN'T SPOKEN TO HIM IN TWO YEARS.
DREADFUL MAN.
RIGHT, I THOUGHT...
AH, YOU THOUGHT YOU WERE GOING TO USE ME
AS A STEPPING STONE, DID YOU?
WELL, TOUGH TITTY.
THAT BRIDGE WAS BURNED A LONG TIME AGO.
BABYSITTER?
YOU'RE STILL IN LOVE
WITH HER, AREN'T YOU?
WE USED TO LOVE PLAYING
SARDINES AT PARTIES, DIDN'T WE, DAD?
OH, YES.
WE USED TO CALL IT AN ICEBREAKER.
DO YOU REMEMBER THE SARDINES SONG?
OF COURSE.
♪ A BABY SARDINE
SAW HIS FIRST SUBMARINE ♪
DON'T YOU DARE SING THAT.
MY HOUSE, I'LL DO WHAT
I BLOODY WELL LIKE.
IS IT JUST ME OR IS THERE LIKE
A SHITTY SMELL IN HERE?
DO YOU REMEMBER THE YEAR WE HAD
THE CUB SCOUTS' JAMBOREE?
CHAOS IT WAS. KIDDIES EVERYWHERE.
THAT WAS A LONG TIME AGO.
WE WERE HAVING SUCH A LAUGH.
AND THEN THIS ONE LITTLE BOY SPOILED IT.
WHAT WAS HIS NAME?
I REALLY THINK WE OUGHT
TO BE MAKING A MOVE NOW.
OH, THE POLICE WERE
INVOLVED AND EVERYTHING.
DO YOU REMEMBER, JOHN?
PHILIP HARRISON.
THAT'S IT, LITTLE PIP.
WHATEVER HAPPENED TO HIM?
FAMILY MOVED AWAY, AS I RECALL.
SPAIN OR SOME SUCH.
MMM, GOOD RIDDANCE, I SAY.
ACCUSING YOU OF SUCH HORRIBLE THINGS.
HE PAID THEM TO GO AWAY.
I WAS TEACHING THE BOY
HOW TO WASH HIMSELF.
BASIC HYGIENE.
WELL, WE WEREN'T ALL THAT LUCKY,
WERE WE, JOHN?
I CAN SMELL CARBOLIC SOAP.
ALL RIGHT, THAT'S ENOUGH!
NOW BEFORE I RING JEREMY KYLE,
CAN I JUST SAY,
THERE'S NO ONE ACTUALLY LOOKING
FOR US ANYMORE. WE'RE ALL HERE.
NO, NO, THAT IAN FELLA'S NOT HERE.
YES, I'VE GOT TO GO AND PICK HIM UP
FROM THE STATION ACTUALLY. SO...
ERM, HE'S IN THE BATHROOM I THINK.
WHAT?
ER, BORING CHAP WITH GLASSES.
OH, NO, THAT'S NOT IAN.
♪ A BABY SARDINE
SAW HIS FIRST SUBMARINE ♪
HELLO.
♪ HE WAS SCARED
AND WATCHED THROUGH THE PEEPHOLE ♪
WHAT'S GOING ON?!
♪ OH COME, COME, COME
SAID THE SARDINE'S MUM ♪
OPEN THIS DOOR.
♪ IT'S ONLY A TIN FULL OF PEOPLE ♪
PIP?